http://www.ochils.com/omc-privacy-policy

HomeJoin The ClubAbout UsThursday Meet LocationsFAQMeetsCalendar ViewFlat ViewExport Meets (as iCal)COVID19 - Outdoor Meets Risk AssessmentClub CottageHow to book the cottageBen More WebcamCottage WeatherCOVID-19 Cottage Instructions and Test and Protect FormCOVID-19 Booking The CottageForumForum ViewRecent TopicsGalleryVisit The GalleryOMC YouTube ChannelView The Front Page PhotosExtrasDownloadsUseful LinksMountain WebcamsBen More Crianlarich WebcamThe OMC OnlineStirling WeatherClimbing GuidesOld ArticlesCurrent Covid RestrictionsContact UsCOVID-19 OfficerFurther Info / New MembersCottage Bookings and InfoContact WebmasterLinksCotswold Outdoor
OMC Privacy Policy
OCHILS MOUNTAINEERING CLUB (“THE CLUB”)
PRIVACY POLICY
By using the Club website, social media pages, contacting the Club about booking the Club Cottage (Inverardran Cottage, Crianlarich, Scotland, FK20 8QS) or by providing information to the Club as part of becoming and being a member of the Club, you consent to the Club collecting and using the information you provide in the way(s) set out in this policy. If you do not agree to this policy please do not use the Club’s website or social media site(s) or try to book/book the Club Cottage. If you are a member of the Club or wish to become a member and don’t agree to this policy please contact the Club Secretary on This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it..
We may make changes to this policy from time to time. If we do so, we will post the changes on the website and they will apply from the time we post them. This policy was last changed on 8 August 2018.
What is personal data?
Personal data is information that can be used to help identify an individual, such as name, address, phone number or email address.
Our privacy policy
It’s important that you read this policy to understand what information we hold, how we may use it, and what your rights are.
We collect information that is either personal data (as outlined above) or non-personal data (such as IP addresses, pages accessed etc).
We collect information about our members, from people who use our social media site(s), from people who use or are interesting in using our Club Cottage and from other people the Club has a relationship with or may need to contact.
We collect information for our organisational purposes, for administrative purposes and to help us in the letting out of beds in the Club Cottage.
We also process members’ personal information in pursuit of our legitimate interests. We give more detail on this below.
We only collect the information that we need or that would be useful to us.
We do our very best to keep personal information secure.
If you are a member, we share your personal data with Mountaineering Scotland to register your membership with them. They then become a controller of your personal data. Mountaineering Scotland provides full details of how it uses your personal data in its own privacy notice (www.mountaineering.scot/privacy-notice) and will not use it for any other purpose.
If you book the Club Cottage we may share your name and telephone number with neighbour(s) at the Club Cottage to allow them to help you if required during your stay.
We also periodically deposit Club documents such as minutes and newsletters (but not membership lists) with Stirling Archives. This means that the names of members may be available to Stirling Archives and through them be publicly available.
We will never share your data with another company or business other than as detailed above or as required by law. We never sell your data.
Legal basis for processing personal data
We rely on various legal bases to justify our processing of your personal data.  Further details of these are set out below.
You have given your consent to the processing of your personal data for the specific purposes mentioned above. You may withdraw your consent to this processing at any time, but this will not affect the lawfulness of any processing of your personal data which was carried out before you withdrew your consent.
The processing is necessary for our legitimate interests. These legitimate interests include:
Providing you with news and updates about the activity of the Club, opportunities to get involved in Club meets, training, business meets, general meetings or other events.
Raising awareness of the Club’s activities by capturing photos or videos. We will use this for promotion, education and development purposes.
Responding to and investigating your questions, comments, support needs, complaints, concerns or allegations.
The processing is necessary to perform a contract to which you are a party or to take steps that you have asked us to take before entering into a contract, such as booking a place on a meet.
The processing is necessary for us, as the data controller, to comply with our legal obligations, such as sharing personal data where we are legally required to do so.
Links to third party websites
Our website contains links to third party websites that we believe may be of interest to our website visitors. This privacy policy only governs our website and we are not responsible for the privacy policies that govern third party websites even where we have provided links to them. If you use any link on our website we recommend you read the privacy policy of that website before sharing any personal or financial data.
Social media sites
We operate a social media page (currently Facebook but we may use others in the future). Although this policy covers how we will use any data collected from those pages it does not cover how the providers of social media websites will use your information. Please ensure you read the privacy policy of the social media website before sharing data and make use of the privacy settings and reporting mechanisms to control how your data is used.
Other people’s data
You may be able to provide the personal data of other people on our social media site(s) or on our website (eg tagging people on photos on social media or using the forums on the website). Before providing anyone else’s data please ensure they are happy for you to do so and under no circumstances must you make public another person’s home address, email address, or phone number.
Your rights
You have certain rights over your data and how we use it. These include:
the right in certain circumstances to have inaccurate personal data rectified, blocked, erased or destroyed
the right to prevent your data being used for direct marketing
the right of access to a copy of the information we hold about you (known as a subject access request)
If you wish to exercise any of these rights please contact the Club Secretary on This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it..
Username
Password
Remember Me
Log in
Forgot Login?
twitter
facebook
envelope
© Copyright 1997 - 2020 Ochils Mountaineering Club | Authors Retain Copyright For Their Submissions | If you Wish To Use Content From This Site Ask Us! Information on this site is provided as-is, with no guarantees either stated or implied about its accuracy or suitability. Your safety is your responsibility!
You can find our privacy policy here
Custom Design by Youjoomla.com
Copyright © Omc2015 2020 All rights reserved. Custom Design by Youjoomla.com
--Export Meets (as iCal)
